Based on the initial survey of the scene,
the victim's wrists
show marks from being bound.
The fatal wound is to the throat.
This is suspected to be gang-related.
Notify the Anti-Triad Unit to assist.
Yes, sir.
Officer Chen.
Well? Is he conscious?
He's conscious.
But his vocal cords are damaged.
So he can't speak for now.
Luckily he's in good shape.
His injuries are lighter than we expected.
But he's only just stabilized.
So don't question him too long.
Alright, thank you.
Tough as nails, aren't you, Bro Pao.
Surviving even this.
I've got to hand it to you.
The forensics report is in.
The victim is Camel.
You did it, didn't you?
You and Camel hacked each other last time.
You couldn't finish him off.
That didn't sit right with you.
This time you pulled it off.
Congratulations, Bro Pao.
Take it easy, Bro Pao.
I know it wasn't you.
You're not that clean and quick.
It was Xie Guanhong.
You're smart.
This time you won't walk away clean.
You survived,
but that's just dumb luck.
But this time, the law will nail you.
All that hard work you put in,
all those years on the job.
Do the math.
Can I put you behind bars
till the day they bury you?
Bro Pao.
Are you hoping to be released on bail?
Will Xie Guanhong let you off, though?
Could it be you dead in the alley next?
If you really want to save your own skin,
then cooperate with the police.
Be my informant.
At least I can plead with the judge.
Try to shave off three to five years.
Like the old saying goes,
he's got no honor, so neither do you.
It's not really betraying your precious code.
Bro Pao.
Your wife's coming by in a bit, too.
What happens if you die?
I'm Inspector Liu Zhenfeng, Major Crimes.
Xie Guanhong isn't home.
We're not here for Xie Guanhong.
Zihao.
What are you doing?
Mom.
What exactly did Zihao do?
What evidence do you have to arrest him?
Xie Zihao is a suspect
in a major murder case.
Please cooperate with the investigation.
Or I'll arrest you along with him.
A Fei, Zihao's been arrested.
All these years I've been coming here,
this place is so old and dirty now.
And that air conditioner...
It smells so weird.
This is bad for your health.
Bad for you, bad for me,
bad for everyone.
Xie Guanhong,
you'd better cooperate.
The evidence is solid.
You killed someone. You can't run.
I own a construction company.
The prices are fair,
and the quality's pretty good too.
How about I fix this place up for you?
I'll definitely do a great job.
You think you're playing the silent game?
Think we're Anti-Triad Unit pushovers?
You're suspected of murder, Mr. Xie.
Sorry I'm late.
May I?
Thank you.
My client
can begin answering questions now.
You say you weren't at the primary scene,
but we collected your footprints there.
There's no point in resisting.
Xie Guanhong,
we already have evidence pointing to you.
Interrogating you now
is just a chance to reduce your sentence.
I didn't have a choice before.
Now I want to be a good guy.
I'm sorry.
I'm a cop.
Calm down!
You've watched too many cop movies.
Bro Pao is already working with us.
He confessed that you killed Camel.
He can testify in court anytime.
Xie Guanhong.
You also burned down Bro Pao's home.
Calm down!
Sorry to interrupt.
Officers,
The evidence you currently hold,
and the witness's testimony,
are not enough to constitute
a complete and valid chain of evidence.
What's more,
your interrogation methods
very likely amount to leading questions.
Once we're in court,
you'll see if this evidence holds up.
When the judge summons you on all this,
you can explain it to the jury.
Sorry to interrupt again.
Officers.
The only witness you have now
is not in a normal, healthy
state capable of rational judgment.
I have the right to suspect
that due to his severe injuries,
he's suffering from delirium.
So his testimony isn't credible enough.
Does it hurt, doing this the whole time?
It's been handed to the Anti-Triad Unit.
The higher-ups told us to pull out.
What?
When did this happen?
Who approved it?
Officer Liu signed it himself.
Looks like our talk today
can come to an end.
No manners.
Bro Pao got hurt.
It's pitiful, yes.
But you can't just...
Whatever they say,
you just believe it.
The bad blood between us,
everyone in the whole company,
who doesn't know about it?
He just wanted to kill me.
Bro Pao's badly injured,
and I'm locked up in here.
Go visit him for me, will you?
Sure.
I'll prepare some gifts
to bring along.
Wipe your shoes clean for the hospital.
Don't cause anyone trouble.
Understood.